[
  {
    "answer": "Good to see you, Donny.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 42,
    "question": "How are you, sir?",
    "qSentId": 41
  },
  {
    "answer": "Feel great.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 44,
    "question": "First up, how are you feeling?",
    "qSentId": 43
  },
  {
    "answer": "Well, I mean, the largest part of the day, 99 percent of the day, is the same as everybody else's day.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 53,
    "question": "What is -- give me the heart -- take me through a day in the life and happening, just what it is to live with this stuff?",
    "qSentId": 52
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tracy is the CEO (ph).",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 58,
    "question": "Tracy runs the show, right?",
    "qSentId": 57
  },
  {
    "answer": "I'm on all kinds of drugs.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 72,
    "question": "You're on -- are you on drugs right now, as we speak?",
    "qSentId": 71
  },
  {
    "answer": "Well, I mean, he's spoken out against science.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 177,
    "question": "He gets in, how does your life get affected?",
    "qSentId": 176
  },
  {
    "answer": "I got the job.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 206,
    "question": "You did get the job, didn't you, because you really didn't sing it that well?",
    "qSentId": 205
  },
  {
    "answer": "You know, I always say he would be converted to being a Democrat now or be in jail.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 227,
    "question": "Would he still be a Republican?",
    "qSentId": 226
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yes, back in the days of Drexel Burnham.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 230,
    "question": "(INAUDIBLE) insider trading?",
    "qSentId": 229
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yes, I do, actually.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 235,
    "question": "I sing like Mitt Romney, you notice that?",
    "qSentId": 234
  },
  {
    "answer": "I think -- I think there's some issues around Gitmo and privacy and some other things like that that I thought -- I thought would be handled by now, just things that can mess around the edges that I thought might have been cleaned up and just from an idealistic point of view.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 251,
    "question": "Such as?",
    "qSentId": 250
  },
  {
    "answer": "I'm not a surrogate.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 262,
    "question": "Has he done enough on stem cell?",
    "qSentId": 261
  },
  {
    "answer": "Well, we can't fund that.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 279,
    "question": "What happens then?",
    "qSentId": 278
  },
  {
    "answer": "You hid it at the beginning.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 300,
    "question": "What?",
    "qSentId": 299
  },
  {
    "answer": "Just don't let -- don't let others project onto you what you're experiencing.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 322,
    "question": "What would you say if there's a young person out there, and just yesterday they found out they have Parkinson's, what would you say to them?",
    "qSentId": 321
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sure, that'd be great.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 350,
    "question": "Can I get you a soda or something, Larry?",
    "qSentId": 349
  },
  {
    "answer": "Parkinson's.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 357,
    "question": "Did you shake that up on purpose?",
    "qSentId": 356
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yes, it was great.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 360,
    "question": "When Larry called you, what did he say, let's do Parkinson's?",
    "qSentId": 359
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yes, yes.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 371,
    "question": "EUTSCH: So in that scene, it's basically, OK, you're going to shake up the Coke, spill it on me, other than that, it's just go and you guys (INAUDIBLE)?",
    "qSentId": 370
  },
  {
    "answer": "He -- well, he's brilliant.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 374,
    "question": "You guys know what you're doing there, don't you?",
    "qSentId": 373
  },
  {
    "answer": "We will be cool in about seven minutes.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 390,
    "question": "So we're cool?",
    "qSentId": 389
  },
  {
    "answer": "I'd like six minutes and 31 seconds.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 402,
    "question": "Can you come back in like a minute, give us a minute?",
    "qSentId": 401
  },
  {
    "answer": "OX: Yes, I mean, sure.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 436,
    "question": "Forget whatever the physical challenges, is there a role that's not going to turn you on that somehow doesn't move the needle for disability or for Parkinson's?",
    "qSentId": 435
  },
  {
    "answer": "I always think the camera can tell.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 510,
    "question": "Ann?",
    "qSentId": 509
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yeah.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 549,
    "question": "You do?",
    "qSentId": 548
  },
  {
    "answer": "Well, I didn't freak out because I knew nothing about the illness.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 554,
    "question": "First time they tell you at 25, what goes through your head?",
    "qSentId": 553
  },
  {
    "answer": "There's no hierarchy of suffering.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 570,
    "question": "What is the key?",
    "qSentId": 569
  },
  {
    "answer": "EUTSCH: We're going to take a break, guys.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 615,
    "question": "So why would they?",
    "qSentId": 614
  },
  {
    "answer": "I think a sense of humor, flexibility and the ability to walk away.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 627,
    "question": "What's the secret, seriously, all kidding aside?",
    "qSentId": 626
  },
  {
    "answer": "I don't mean -- I mean walk away from bad moments.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 630,
    "question": "What the heck does that mean?",
    "qSentId": 629
  },
  {
    "answer": "No, we don't have enough time to help me.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 642,
    "question": "Does that help you in your own?",
    "qSentId": 641
  },
  {
    "answer": "Planned Parenthood for the Christian right is a symbol.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 654,
    "question": "You see that ad, forget politics aside, what is your reaction, just from getting somebody elected?",
    "qSentId": 653
  },
  {
    "answer": "I agree with you.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 664,
    "question": "They can't win this way?",
    "qSentId": 663
  },
  {
    "answer": "I have never seen the Republican party dragged this far to the right in the primary process.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 674,
    "question": "But is it going to come back to bite them?",
    "qSentId": 673
  },
  {
    "answer": "To this extent, no.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 694,
    "question": "Have you seen anything like this?",
    "qSentId": 693
  },
  {
    "answer": "The NIH budget is frozen at about 30 billion dollars, which pays for about 2.5 months in Afghanistan.",
    "docId": "120314pmt",
    "aSentId": 706,
    "question": "So as somebody who obviously wants everything to be cured, but M.S. is clearly going to be first on your list, how do you come to terms with that?",
    "qSentId": 705
  }
]